A. James Delahoussaye collection of Atchafalaya River Basin recordings
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series III: Photographs
  - Photographs from Bailey Albert and Agnes Sauce Bailey
    - Marcelette Bailey Paray, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph116.jpg
    - Marla Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph117.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph118.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph119.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph120.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange Bailey's house, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph121.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph122.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph123.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph124.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph125.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph126.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph127.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph128.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph129.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Hester Lange, September 20, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph130.jpg
    - Milton Benoit Bailey and Lily Hester Lange, September 7, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph131.jpg
    - Myrtle Bigler and Harold Bigler, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph132.jpg
    - Preston Sauce, Agnes Sauce, Robert Sauce, and Ida Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph133.jpg
    - Ricky Higgins, James "Hockey" Higgins, and Milton Bailey, August 10, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph134.jpg
    - Robert J. Sauce and Gertrude Duvall Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph135.jpg
    - Robert J. Sauce, August 25, 1942, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph136.jpg
    - Rodolph Bailey (son of Ernestine and Wilson Bailey), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph137.jpg
    - Rosalie Sauce and Berinda Millet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph138.jpg
    - Roy "Bootsie" Millet, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph139.jpg
    - Sap Couvillier, Jerry Marcotte, and Harry Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph140.jpg
    - Vicki Marcotte at age 5 months, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph141.jpg
    - Warren Blaine Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph142.jpg
    - Warren Blaine Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph143.jpg
  - Photographs from Dorothy Bailey Couvillier
    - Lena, Dorothy, Jack, Carlin, and Arthur (Couvillier?), and Leona, Gloria, Shirley, and Loue, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph144.jpg
    - Unidentified residents of the Atchafalaya Basin, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph145.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., 1928, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph146.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., 1932, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph147.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph148.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., circa 1960s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph149.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., circa 1960s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph150.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., November 1948, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph151.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph152.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey, circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph153.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph154.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Agnes Bailey, Justin Couvillier, Larry Couvillier, Bonita Couvillier, and Darlene Soulé, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph155.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier and Dot Couvillier, June 1,1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph156.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier and Lula Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph157.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph158.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph159.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph160.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph161.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. and Dot's house, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph162.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. and Larry Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph163.jpg
    - Albert Bailey Sr., Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier, and Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph164.jpg
    - Albert Bailey Jr., Dorothy Bailey, and Agnes Bailey, circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph165.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph166.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph167.jpg
    - Albert "Putt" Couvillier, Arthur "Hoss" Couvillier, Irene Couvillier, Clifton Couvillier, and Shirl, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph168.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. and Kent Bailey, 1961, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph169.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey, circa 1950s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph170.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph171.jpg
    - Belinda Couvillier, Melodye Couvillier, and Kim Couvillier, December 1961, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph172.jpg
    - Berinda Ann Millet, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph173.jpg
    - Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph174.jpg
    - Bradley Daigle (son of Norman who was killed in Vietnam), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph175.jpg
    - Bryan Couvillier, Karen Couvillier, Kim Couvillier, Ruby Couvillier, and Melodye Couvillier, 1962, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph176.jpg
    - Buddy Vice, Laura Ann Vice, and Albert Vice, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph177.jpg
    - Claudia Hazen (teacher), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph178.jpg
    - Clifton Couvillier and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph179.jpg
    - Clifton Couvillier and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph180.jpg
    - Clifton Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph181.jpg
    - Clifton Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph182.jpg
    - Clifton Couvillier, Arthur Louviere, Arthur Couvillier, and Charles Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph183.jpg
    - Darlene Bailey, Dorothy Bailey, Gloria Lange, and Juanita Doucet, 1956, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph184.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey and "Albert Putt" Couvillier, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph185.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey and Putt Couvillier, December 12, 1922, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph186.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey and Rochelle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph187.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph188.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1956, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph189.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey at age 14, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph190.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey at fence in Albert Couvillier's yard, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph191.jpg
    - Elda Mae Verrett, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph192.jpg
    - Ella Couvillier, George Alberta, and Mary Alberta, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph193.jpg
    - Ella Couvillier, George Alberta, and family, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph194.jpg
    - Ernestine Bailey Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph195.jpg
    - Eula Daigle Mire and Angeline Bailey Burns, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph196.jpg
    - Floyd Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph197.jpg
    - Gwen Couvillier, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph198.jpg
    - Herbert Bourliea and Lisa Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph199.jpg
    - Howard Lopez and Myrtle Couvillier Lopez, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph200.jpg
    - Irene Couvillier and Abner Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph201.jpg
    - Irene Couvillier, Clifton Couvillier, and Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph202.jpg
    - Irene Couvillier, Newton Aucoin, and Albert "Putt' Couvillier, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph203.jpg
    - Irene Couvillier, Violet Couvillier, Hoss Couvillier, and Clifton Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph204.jpg
    - James "Hockey" Higgins, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph205.jpg
    - Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph206.jpg
    - Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., Lester Couvillier, Sr., Albert "Putt" Couvillier, and Lula, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph207.jpg
    - Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, Carl Couvillier, and Clifton Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph208.jpg
    - Joseph "Sun" Burns and Lester Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph209.jpg
    - Juanita Doucet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph210.jpg
    - Justin Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph211.jpg
    - Karen Couvillier, Melodye Couvillier, Lloyd Couvillier, Kim Couvillier, Lula Couvillier, and Denise Couvillier, 1962, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph212.jpg
    - Kent Bailey, 1964, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph213.jpg
    - Kim and Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph214.jpg
    - Kim and Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph215.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1962, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph216.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph217.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph218.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph219.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph220.jpg
    - Kim Couvillier and Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph221.jpg
    - Lena Mae Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph222.jpg
    - Leona "Puna" Sauce, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph223.jpg
    - Lester Couvillier and Lula Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph224.jpg
    - Lester Couvillier and Lula Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph225.jpg
    - Lester Couvillier and others, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph226.jpg
    - Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr. and Shirley Boudreaux, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph227.jpg
    - Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph228.jpg
    - Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph229.jpg
    - Lester Couvillier, Sr., Floyd, and Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph230.jpg
    - Lola Mae and Berinda Ann Millet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph231.jpg
    - Lula Myers Couvillier and Mrs. Gilmore, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph232.jpg
    - Lula Myers Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph233.jpg
    - Lula Myers Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph234.jpg
    - Lula Myers Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph235.jpg
    - Lula Myers Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph236.jpg
    - Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph237.jpg
    - Marvin Louviere, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph238.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier and Gwen Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph239.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, Albert "Putt" Couvillier, Milton Bailey, and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph240.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier and Darlene Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph241.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph242.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph243.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph244.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph245.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier and Kent Bailey, August 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph246.jpg
    - Melodye Couvillier and Kim Couvillier, 1961, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph247.jpg
    - Milton Bailey crabbing, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph248.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph249.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph250.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph251.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph252.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, Rochelle Gandolf, and Jesse Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph253.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Rochelle Gandolf, July 1949, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph254.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph255.jpg
    - Milton "Butsy" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph256.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Hester Bailey, June 1,1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph257.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, Hester Bailey, Albert Couvillier, Dot Couvillier, and Gloria Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph258.jpg
    - Momo Daigle, Corey Bailey, and Lena Mae Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph259.jpg
    - Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., Lula Myers Couvillier, and Irene Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph260.jpg
    - Putt and Dot and Kim and Melodye, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph261.jpg
    - Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph262.jpg
    - Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph263.jpg
    - Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph264.jpg
    - Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph265.jpg
    - Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph266.jpg
    - Agnes at Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph267.jpg
    - Duty and Marvin Louviere at Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph268.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte and Albert Bailey at Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph269.jpg
    - Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier, Agnes Sauce Bailey, Marvin, and Duty at Putt's Birthday, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph270.jpg
    - Ricky Higgins, Hockey Higgins, and Milton Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph271.jpg
    - Rochelle Gandolf, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph272.jpg
    - Rosalie Sauce (Agnes's mother), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph273.jpg
    - Roy "Bootsie" Millet, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph274.jpg
    - Ruby Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph275.jpg
  - Photographs from Edward and Lena Mae Bailey Couvillier
    - Abner Couvillier, Charles Couvillier, Larry Couvillier, and Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph276.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph277.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey, Alberta Bailey, and Albert Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph278.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph279.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph280.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr. and Brent, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph281.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph282.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph283.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph284.jpg
    - Albert Jr. and Brent Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph285.jpg
    - Bonita Couvillier, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph286.jpg
    - Corey, Kim, Kevin Couvillier, Gwen Couvillier, Lynwood "Peanut" Couvillier, Warren, Brent, Melodye Couvillier, and Trevor, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph287.jpg
    - Dot Bailey, Alberta Bailey, and Hester Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph288.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier at ages 3 to 12, circa 1930s, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph289.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier and Carlin Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph290.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier, Harry Lange, Milton Bailey, Earl Hunter, and DJ Ponv, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph291.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier, Leona "Puna" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph292.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier and Joseph "Son" Couvillier, circa 1931, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph293.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier, Justin Couvillier, Larry Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph294.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier, -Lena Mae Couvillier at age 18, and Lena at age 19, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph295.jpg
    - Edward Couvillier, Albert Couvillier, Abner Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph296.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph297.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph298.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier and Albert Couvillier, 1938, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph299.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier and Eljean Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph300.jpg
    - Ernestine Daigle and Homer Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph301.jpg
    - Families of Myette Point, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph302.jpg
    - Gertie Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph303.jpg
    - Gertie Persilver Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph304.jpg
    - Gloria Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph305.jpg
    - Gloria Lange, Edward Couvillier, and Dot Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph306.jpg
    - Gwen Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph307.jpg
    - Hester Lange, circa 1950, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph308.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte, Edward Couvillier, and Floyd Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph309.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte and Alberta Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph310.jpg
    - Jerry Marcotte and Alberta Marcotte, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph311.jpg
    - Joseph "Son" Couvillier (son of Albert), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph312.jpg
    - Justin Couvillier, Bonita Couvillier, Lena Mae Couvillier, Harry Lange, and Larry Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph313.jpg
    - Justin Couvillier and Larry Couvillier, circa 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph314.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier and children at Keelboat Pass, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph315.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, Blankenship and Verrettat Keelboat Pass, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph316.jpg
    - Henry Larson, Albert Couvillier, and Raymond at Keelboat Pass, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph317.jpg
    - Larry Couvillier, circa 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph318.jpg
    - Larry Couvillier and Bonita Couvillier, circa 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph319.jpg
    - Lena Mae Couvillier, circa 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph320.jpg
    - Meyon, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph321.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, Clifton Couvillier, and Edward Couvillier, circa 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph322.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, Milton "Butsy" Sauce, Clifton Couvillier, and Lester "Noochie" Couvillier, Jr., circa 1952, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph323.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph324.jpg
    - Milton Bailey, Albert "Putt" Couvillier, and Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph325.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Russell, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph326.jpg
    - Leona "Puna" Sauce Russell and Bonita Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph327.jpg
    - Jesse "Sap" Couvillier, Milton, and Edward Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph328.jpg
    - Alberta, Leona "Puna" Sauce Russell, Hester Lange Bailey, and Tot at the Schoolhouse, circa 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph329.jpg
    - Schoolhouse, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph330.jpg
    - Schoolhouse, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph331.jpg
    - William 'Bill' Sanders and daughter Ella, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph332.jpg
  - Photographs from Gwen Couvillier
    - Agnes Sauce Bailey at age 15, 1927, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph333.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph334.jpg
    - Ella and Albert Couvillier, circa 1949, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph335.jpg
    - Gwen Zirlott, Jake Zirlott, Kent Bailey, and Robert Bailey, August 7, 1983, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph336.jpg
    - Gwen Zirlott, Jake Zirlott, Kent Bailey, and Robert Bailey, August 7, 1983, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph337.jpg
    - Gwen Zirlott and Jake Zirlott, August 7, 1983, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph338.jpg
    - Gwen Couvillier at age 7, 1965, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph339.jpg
    - Kent Bailey and Robert Bailey, August 7, 1983, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph340.jpg
    - Milton Bailey and Carlin Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph341.jpg
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph342.jpg
    - Albert Bailey and Agnes Bailey, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph343.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey, Milton Bailey, and Hester Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph344.jpg
    - Alberta Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph345.jpg
    - Aurelia Vining, Mary Alberta, unidentified, and George Alberta, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph346.jpg
    - Dan Lange and Viola Lange, 1935, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph347.jpg
    - Dan Lange and Viola Lange, August 10, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph348.jpg
    - Dan Lange, Viola Lange, Harry Lange, Juanita Lange, and Pete Doucet, August 10, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph349.jpg
    - Darlene Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph350.jpg
    - Dawn Hebert, Hester Bailey, and Larry Couvillier, June 1968, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph351.jpg
    - Ella S. Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph352.jpg
    - Elton Hebert and Milton Bailey, June 1968, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph353.jpg
    - Hester Bailey and Darlene Bailey at Charenton Beach, 1956, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph354.jpg
    - Kent Bailey and Darlene Bailey, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph355.jpg
    - Kent Bailey and Darlene Bailey, June 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph356.jpg
    - L. Darlene Bailey, 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph357.jpg
    - Tugboat "Baby Dot", 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph358.jpg
    - Viola Lange and Dan Lange, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph359.jpg
    - Viola Couvillier at age 16, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph360.jpg
    - Viola Lange, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph361.jpg
    - William Sanders, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph362.jpg
  - Photographs from Huey Daigle
    - Agnes Bailey and Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph363.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1956, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph364.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph365.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Sr., 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph366.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr., Carol Bailey, and Justin Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph367.jpg
    - Carol Ann Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph368.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1946, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph369.jpg
    - Dorothy Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph370.jpg
    - Jesse Daigle, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph371.jpg
    - Joseph Sauce, Jr., 1956, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph372.jpg
  - Photographs from Jack and Helen Aucion Sauce
    - Children with dog, 1944, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph373.jpg
    - Abner Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph374.jpg
    - Melvin, Wilton "Honk," Wilton "Jack" Sauce, Gloria Lange, and Shirley Gondolfo, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph375.jpg
    - Eldora "Fadolia" Sauce and Elton Sauce, 1944, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph376.jpg
    - Eldora "Fadolia" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph377.jpg
    - Ella Sanders and William Sanders, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph378.jpg
    - Ella "Tot" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph379.jpg
    - Elton Sauce and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph380.jpg
    - Elton Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph381.jpg
    - Elton Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph382.jpg
    - Elton Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph383.jpg
    - Joseph Sauce and Vina Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph384.jpg
    - Joseph Sauce and Vina Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph385.jpg
    - Leona 'Puna' Sauce, 1949, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph386.jpg
    - M. Vina C. Sauce, 1950, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph387.jpg
    - Mary Lee "T-Put" Sauce, 1949, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph388.jpg
    - Mary Lee 'T-Put" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph389.jpg
    - Milton "Butsy" Sauce at age 16, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph390.jpg
    - Milton "Butsy" Sauce at age 18, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph391.jpg
    - Milton "Butsy" Sauce, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph392.jpg
    - Sauce children, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph393.jpg
    - Steve, Milton Sauce, Abner Couvillier, Vina Sauce, Grandma Ella, Alberta, Harry Lange, and Milton Bailey, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph394.jpg
    - Vina Sauce and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph395.jpg
  - Photographs from Louella "Duddy" Verrett Louviere
    - Unidentified, Bessie Burns, Ella Couvillier, and unidentified, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph396.jpg
    - Abner Couvillier, January 6, 1960, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph397.jpg
    - Abner Couvillier at age 18, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph398.jpg
    - Abner Couvillier and Annie Sanders, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph399.jpg
    - Abner Couvillier and Ubert Neck, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph400.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, Mrs. and Albert "Putt" Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph401.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier and Mrs (Putt's maternal grandma) Couvillier, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph402.jpg
    - Albert (son of Rose), 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph403.jpg
    - Albert Bailey, Jr. and Elda Mae Verrett, 1955, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph404.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, November 22, 1958, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph405.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph406.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier, 1957, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph407.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier married Mrs. Gilmore, November 8, 1959, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph408.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier and Louella Verrett, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph409.jpg
    - Albert Couvillier's house at Myette Point, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph410.jpg
    - Albert 'Putt' Couvillier, 1953, 1 JPEG file; afc2012044_ph411.jpg